TEJAS DHARMA KAMBLE

kambletejas1999@gmail.com \$\square\$ 9930208155 \$\square\$ Mumbai, Maharashtra \$\frac{\pi}{\pi}\$ 29 May 1999

m www.linkedin.com/in/kamble-tejas99 📕 Indian 🕠 https://github.com/tejaskamble99

Profile

Looking forward to earning the position of Software Developer at a leading organization to showcase my skills in programming to generate high-end solutions to general software issues along with drawing better user experience.

skills

Frontend:-, HTML ,CSS ,Tailwind ,Javascript ,React Js

Backend, Node Js, Express Js, Django

Database, MySql, MongoDB, PostgreSQL

Data analysis skills, Pandas, PowerBI, Excel, Data cleaning, EDA, ETL, Python

Professional Experience

Software Developer Internship, Cloud Connection, Remote

Jan 2024 - present

- Engineered responsive user interfaces using React, resulting in a 25% increase in user engagement
- Developed and optimized reusable UI components, reducing development time by 30%

Data Analysis Using python internship, Vault of Codes, remote

Feb 2024 - Feb 2024

- Implemented Python scripts for data visualization in Tableau, reducing report generation time by 50% and enabling the marketing team to make data-driven decisions resulting in a 15% increase in lead conversion rates.
- Use python library for data reading and visualisation such as pandas, numpy, Matplotlib

Projects

Realtime-chatapp ∂

• Description: Develope a Realtime-Chat App using ReactJs ,SocketIO , Express

TODO APP, Description: Developed a ToDo list application using React and Redux for state management. \mathscr{D}

- Led end-to-end development of ToDo list app using React and Redux.
- Implemented core features including task creation, deletion, and status updates.
- Technologies Used: React ,Redux ,Material-UI,JavaScript (ES6+),HTML5/CSS3

Stock market predictions using LSMT model @

2023

- · Languages and Frameworks: Django, HTML, CSS, Javascript
- using python created the Machine Learning model to predict the future price

Store Sales and Profit Analysis using Python *⊘*

 Conducted a comprehensive Data Analysis on store sales data using Python, employing techniques such as data cleaning, exploratory data analysis (EDA), and visualization.

covid vacation and deaths Analysis Dashboard &

Software uses:- tableau public , My SQL server , Excel

Certificates

- Python Comprehensive Bootcamp (Beginner To Professional)
- accenture Virtual Experience Program on Forage - August 2023
- Programming with Python Ø
- React: All You Need to Know with Practical Project
- SQL Masterclass: SQL for Data Analytics
- pwc switzerland Virtual Experience Program on Forage - August 2023
- J.P. Morgan Software Engineering Virtual Experience on Forage -March 2024
- Data Analyst Boot camp 2023
- JPMorgan Chase & Co. Virtual Experience Program on Forage September 2023 *∂*

Education

Master of Science (M.Sc), Information Technology, M.L. Dahanukar College

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc), Information Technology,

Lords Universal College CGPA: 8.28/10 2021 - 2024 | mumbai, india

2018 - 2021 | Mumbai, India